[Music]
that was great we got it terrific do you
want to rap or do you want to punch
anybody out that's pretty Irish did you
see what just happened with my
wife your ex-wife is a nut
job
what look the Irish suffer that's in
their blood okay it's
tradition and you know what else you're
the one who told me about the guy who
waited and waited and waited and waited
until a little bit of fungus turned into
penicillin and this Irish sequence is
very close to becoming
penicillin thanks to you is that all you
have to say well those were your words
and I think they say a
lot you know
Grant when I started here I believed in
what we were doing
well now I'm not so sure but there's one
thing I do know you're the biggest jag
off I've ever worked for and I hope this
place Burns to the Grind with you in it
cuz that's exactly what you deserve you
nickel and dime chicken
mother you call yourself a producer you
couldn't produce a ham sandwich and I am
walking out that door and I am never
coming back now if you beg me I
quit yeah one more time
cat him don't let him get away far don't
let him get away do you have
them okay weirdly enough Forest has
actually not been seen by anyone here at
the show since that night so
it seems like he really did quit for
real which is obviously very
[Music]
unprofessional